	var quizArrayAddition = [{
		"id":"0",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"1",
		"question":"1 + 1 = ?",
		"choice1":"3",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"1",
		"correct":"2"
	},
	{
		"id":"1",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"2",
		"question":"2 + 2 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"5",
		"correct":"4"
	},
	{
		"id":"2",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"1",
		"question":"2 + 1 = ?",
		"choice1":"2",
		"choice2":"1",
		"choice3":"3",
		"correct":"3"
	},
	{
		
		"id":"3",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"3",
		"question":"2 + 3 = ?",
		"choice1":"3",
		"choice2":"4",
		"choice3":"5",
		"correct":"5"
	},
	{
		"id":"4",
		"q1":"3",
		"q2":"3",
		"question":"3 + 3 = ?",
		"choice1":"6",
		"choice2":"4",
		"choice3":"0",
		"correct":"6"
	},
	{
		"id":"5",
		"q1":"4",
		"q2":"2",
		"question":"4 + 2 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"6"
	},
	{
		"id":"6",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"1",
		"question":"1 + 1 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"2"
	},
	{
		"id":"7",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"2",
		"question":"1 + 2 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"3",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"3"
	},
	{
		"id":"8",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"3",
		"question":"1 + 3 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"4"
	},
	{
		"id":"9",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"4",
		"question":"1 + 4 = ?",
		"choice1":"5",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"5"
	},
	{
		"id":"10",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"5",
		"question":"1 + 5 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"6"
	},
	{
		"id":"11",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"6",
		"question":"1 + 6 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"7",
		"correct":"7"
	},
	{
		"id":"12",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"7",
		"question":"1 + 7 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"8",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"8"
	},
	{
		"id":"13",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"8",
		"question":"1 + 8 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"9",
		"correct":"9"
	},
	{
		"id":"14",
		"q1":"1",
		"q2":"9",
		"question":"1 + 9 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"10",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"10"
	},
	{
		"id":"15",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"1",
		"question":"2 + 1 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"3",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"3"
	},
	{
		"id":"16",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"2",
		"question":"2 + 2 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"4"
	},
	{
		"id":"17",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"3",
		"question":"2 + 3 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"5",
		"correct":"5"
	},
	{
		"id":"18",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"4",
		"question":"2 + 4 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"6"
	},
	{
		"id":"19",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"5",
		"question":"2 + 5 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"7",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"7"
	},
	{
		"id":"20",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"6",
		"question":"2 + 6 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"8",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"8"
	},
	{
		"id":"21",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"7",
		"question":"2 + 7 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"9",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"9"
	},
	{
		"id":"22",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"8",
		"question":"2 + 8 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"10",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"10"
	},
	{
		"id":"23",
		"q1":"2",
		"q2":"9",
		"question":"2 + 9 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"11",
		"correct":"11"
	},
	{
		"id":"24",
		"q1":"3",
		"q2":"1",
		"question":"3 + 1 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"4"
	},
	{
		"id":"25",
		"q1":"3",
		"q2":"2",
		"question":"3 + 2 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"5",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"5"
	},
	{
		"id":"26",
		"q1":"3",
		"q2":"3",
		"question":"3 + 3 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"6"
	},
	{
		"id":"27",
		"q1":"3",
		"q2":"4",
		"question":"3 + 4 = ?",
		"choice1":"7",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"7"
	},
	{
		"id":"28",
		"q1":"3",
		"q2":"5",
		"question":"3 + 5 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"8",
		"correct":"8"
	},
	{
		"id":"29",
		"q1":"3",
		"q2":"6",
		"question":"3 + 6 = ?",
		"choice1":"4",
		"choice2":"9",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"9"
	},
	{
		"id":"30",
		"q1":"3",
		"q2":"7",
		"question":"3 + 7 = ?",
		"choice1":"10",
		"choice2":"2",
		"choice3":"6",
		"correct":"10"
	}
	]
	
	